我就没受过什么特别待遇啊
I never got any special treatment.
那我想你应该知道为什么吧
I think you can do the math there.
靠
Damn.
那你这么想
Well, think of it this way:
就像是在健身房锻炼
It's like doing reps at a gym.
你得一直反复练同样的动作
Doing something over and over again
这样才能练出炸裂般的胸肌啊
is how you make your pecs pop.
我唯一有兴趣锻炼的肌肉只有我的大脑
The only muscle I care to work out is my brain.
那你就好好反复锻炼直到大脑炸裂啊
Then get those reps in and make that brain pop.
炸炸炸  裂裂裂
Pop, pop. Pop, pop, pop.
你刚才描述的是脑动脉瘤破裂吧
What you're describing is an aneurism.
炸炸炸  裂裂裂
Pop, pop. Pop, pop, pop.
正式宣布  我又坠入爱河啦
It's official! I'm in love.
我刚跟我的梦中情人度过美好的一晚
I just spent the night with the woman of my dreams.
你在离婚派对上认识的那女人吗
The lady from your divorce party?
对啊  她是我的灵魂伴侣
Yeah. She's my soulmate.
她很有趣  她很美丽
She's funny. She's beautiful.
-身上几乎没有什么疤痕  -哎哟妈呀
- She has almost no scars. - Hot biscuits.